Guide to the Lynne Tillman Papers 1939-2008 (Bulk 1984-2006) MSS.180
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XIII: Other Works and Activities, 193245
  - Series XIII, Subseries C: Publicity, 193299
    - Joe Tabbi - mentions of Lynne Tillman, 2003; 193353 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - "John and Yoko Piece" - Soho News by Amy Taubin; Lynne Tillman quoted, 1980; 193352 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Kasia Brody interviews Lynne Tillman - article "No Innocent Abroad: The Fiction of Lynne Tillman" to promote Cast in Doubt, 1994; 193351 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Lin Gillan interviews Lynne Tillman - Brighton, 1994; 193350 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Lisa Dierbeck interview with Lynne Tillman - Rain Taxi, 1998; 193349 (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Living with Contradictions - press, 1983; 193348 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Living with Contradictions publicity, 1985; 193347 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Living with Contradictions publicity - published by Top Stories edited and published by Anne Turyn, 1986; 193346 (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Living with Contradictions reviews, 1985-1987; 193345 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - Lynne Tillman Anthology - press and publicity, 1984-1992; 193344 (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - Lynne Tillman event publicity, 1979; 193343 (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - "Lynne Tillman: Fortsatter att vara rebell" - Hanriette Zorn for Swedish magazine Bibel, 1998; 193342 (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - Lynne Tillman mentions, 1987-1998; 193341 (Box 32, Folder 50)
    - Lynne Tillman press, 1997; 193340 (Box 32, Folder 51)
    - Lynne Tillman publicity, 2001; 193339 (Box 32, Folder 52)
    - Madame Realism - Lynne Tillman and Kiki Smith; exhibited in Un Libro Mas Para el Archivero - international exhibit of artists books, Undated; 193338 (Box 32, Folder 53)
    - Matisse, Boss of Bosses, Ciabattari - reviews and criticism, 1990-1993; 193337 (Box 32, Folder 54)
    - Mentions of Lynne Tillman, Undated; 193336 (Box 32, Folder 55)
    - Mentions of Lynne Tillman in press and publicity, Undated; 193335 (Box 32, Folder 56)
    - Mentions of Lynne Tillman in press - not reviews of her work, Undated; 193334 (Box 32, Folder 57)
    - Modern Fiction Studies - Postmodernism issue - Robert Siegle's essay references Lynne Tillman, 1995; 193333 (Box 32, Folder 58)
    - The New Gothic - "A Dead Summer", 1991; 193332 (Box 32, Folder 59)
    - O.J. Simpson article in German Vogue, 1995; 193331 (Box 32, Folder 60)
    - Paranoid's Annonymous Newsletter - press and publicity, 1976; 193330 (Box 32, Folder 61)
    - Paradoid's Annonymous Newsletter - press releases, Undated; 193329 (Box 32, Folder 62)
    - Patrick McGrath interviews Lynne Tillman for Bomb magazine, 1991; 193328 (Box 32, Folder 63)
      Article removed to Oversize
    - Patrick McGrath interviews Lynne Tillman for Bomb, Undated; 193327 (Box 32, Folder 64)
    - Peter Nichols interviews Lynne Tillman, 1995; 193326 (Box 32, Folder 65)
    - Peter Nichols interviews Lynne Tillman in Textual Practice, 1995; 193325 (Box 32, Folder 66)
    - Press Release for Franklin Furnace reading "Weird Fucks" - draft and final, Undated; 193324 (Box 32, Folder 67)
    - Prose in General - including Lynne Tillman, Undated; 193323 (Box 32, Folder 68)
    - Publicity for Madame Realism - Lynne Tillman and Kiki Smith, Undated; 193322 (Box 32, Folder 69)
    - Publicity - including reviews, invites, and contacts, 1992-1996; 193321 (Box 32, Folder 70)
    - Publicity, 2002; 193320 (Box 32, Folder 71)
    - Publicity, 2003; 193319 (Box 32, Folder 72)
    - Publicity, 2004; 193318 (Box 32, Folder 73)
    - Publicity, 2005; 193317 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Publicity, Undated; 193316 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Publicity - including resume, 2001; 193315 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Reviews of Anthologies which include Lynne Tillman, Undated; 193314 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Reviews - Head Shots, 1996; 193313 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Review - Head Shots, 1996; 193312 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Sex and the City Anthology - reviews and publicity, 2001; 193311 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Smith, Kiki - Believer interview with Lynne Tillman, 2004; 193310 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - "Stories and Essays for Sleepless Nights" press, 1996; 193309 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Suburban Ambush - promotion and reviews, 1989; 193308 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Sunday Afternoon Poetry at La Locandadi Giotto Cafe, 1985; 193307 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Temporary Culture #6 - publicity for "Disorderly Conduct" in Voice Literary Supplement Fiction Reader, Undated; 193306 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Texts of introductions for Lynne Tillman, Undated; 193305 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Transcript - R.S. interviews Lynne Tillman, Undated; 193304 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Ulf Peter Hallberg interviews Lynne Tillman in Idag, 1992; 193303 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - "Weird Fucks" publicity, 1984; 193302 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - What Does She Want video series - publicity and Lynne Tillman's notes, 1988; 193301 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Yvonne Rainer - Wexner, Undated; 193300 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Series XIII, Subseries D: Notes and Fragments, 193273
    - Assorted Lynne Tillman notes on postcards, Undated; 193298 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - "Conferences, etc; ephemera" - in folder - Porkopolis pamphlet, How do I Look?, Lesbian/Gay Film/Video series, Undated; 193297 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - David Hofstra: The Dixie Peppers, Undated; 193296 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Diary? - Notes for Cast in Doubt and Haunted Houses, Undated; 193295 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Dream Journal entry, Oct 24; 193294 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Four Tuesdays in September portable poetry project - including Lynne Tillman, Undated; 193293 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Fragments of MO essay, Undated; 193292 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Franklin Furnace - "1977: From the Archive", Undated; 193291 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - "Lost at Sea and Cast in Doubt" - Notes on Lynne Tillman's fiction, Undated; 193290 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Moo Tour - Virtual Space - Kearsley, Chad, 1996; 193289 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Notes for Cast in Doubt or Haunted Houses, Undated; 193288 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Notes and Clippings, Undated; 193287 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Notes and Fragments, Undated; 193286 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Notes and Fragments, Undated; 193285 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Paradoid's Annonymous Newsletter meeting notes, Undated; 193284 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Paranoid's Ball, Undated; 193283 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Photocopy of the cover of "Earth Angel" by Lynne Tillman, Undated; 193282 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Renee Green - "Contact Zone", Undated; 193281 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Responses to Haunted Houses, Motion Sickness, and Committed, Undated; 193280 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Stroemfeld Verlag publishing catalogue - Lynne Tillman German translations, 1993-1994; 193279 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Top Stories reading - Lynne Tillman's Madame Realism, Undated; 193278 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Uncontrollable Bodies, Undated; 193277 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Voice Literary Supplement - War of the Words anthology including Lynne Tillman, Undated; 193276 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Writing ideas: Elizabeth, etc..., Undated; 193275 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - "Wrong in the Past", "It was Ramadan..." fragments - pages 1-3, Undated; 193274 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Series XIII, Subseries E: Teaching, 193246
    - 2003 Teaching assignments memo, 2002; 193272 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Bard College, 1994-2005; 193271 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Bard MFA - administrative material, 1999; 193270 (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Bard: Sager, Trey "Punk Traffic" - MFA thesis, 2003; 193269 (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Barnard, 2001-2005; 193268 (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Brown University, 1998; 193267 (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - The City College of New York, 1992; 193266 (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Columbia University, 1998; 193265 (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - Cullen, Catherine - Bard, 1996; 193264 (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Faculty Appointment at Barnard College, 2005; 193263 (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - Fiction Workshop, 1994; 193262 (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - Johns Hopkins University, 1998-1999; 193261 (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - Lang, Joel - "Suicide Swine Collection of Stories" - MFA Thesis statement (Bard), 2003; 193260 (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - Literature Initiative in Technology - "The Other Modernism" web based course, 1997; 193259 (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - Los Angeles Contemporary Exhibitions readings including Lynne Tillman, 1986; 193258 (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - Manhattanville College, 2005; 193257 (Box 33, Folder 59)
    - Princeton University, 1997-2001; 193256 (Box 33, Folder 60)
    - Queens College, 1999; 193255 (Box 33, Folder 61)
    - South East Arts, 1993; 193254 (Box 33, Folder 62)
    - Sussex - visiting lecturer, 1994; 193253 (Box 33, Folder 63)
    - Teaching Correspondence including letters of recommendation, 1996; 193252 (Box 33, Folder 64)
    - Teaching: Hofstra University - Summer Writers' Conference, 1994; 193251 (Box 33, Folder 65)
    - University of Sussex at Brighton, 1994-1995; 193250 (Box 33, Folder 66)
    - Workshop Proposal, Undated; 193249 (Box 33, Folder 67)
    - Yale Graduate School of Arts - students, Undated; 193248 (Box 33, Folder 68)
    - Yale University School of Arts, 1996-2004; 193247 (Box 33, Folder 69)
- Series XIV: Education, 193194
  Series XIV: Education contains materials from Lynne Tillman's time in school. These include syllabi, essays, and required reading for Tillman's secondary, undergraduate, and graduate education. This series is divided into two subseries:
  A: Secondary and Undergraduate
  B: Sociology Coursework
  - Series XIV, Subseries A: Secondary and Undergraduate, 193227
    - "A Closer Look at my Talk...", 1987; 193244 (Box 33, Folder 70)
    - Brief papers for Women/French Literature course, 1982; 193243 (Box 33, Folder 71)
    - Critical Fiction / Critical Self - Bakhtin, Undated; 193242 (Box 33, Folder 72)
    - Ethnolinguistics - Notes and paper: "A closer look at my talk, or...", 1987; 193241 (Box 33, Folder 73)
    - Feminism, Film, Looking, Psychoanalysis - articles (1 of 2), Undated; 193240 (Box 33, Folder 74)
    - Feminism, Film, Looking, Psychoanalysis - articles (2 of 2), Undated; 193239 (Box 33, Folder 75)
    - Foucault notes - for Dr. Rotenberg, Deviance Theory, 1983; 193238 (Box 33, Folder 76)
    - Gender Readings - notes, syllabus, reading, Undated; 193237 (Box 33, Folder 77)
    - Lawrencian - Lawrence High School yearbook - Lynne Tillman was the editor, 1962; 193236 (Box 33, Folder 78)
    - Modernism/Postmodernism articles, Undated; 193235 (Box 33, Folder 79)
    - "Others Papers", Undated; 193234 (Box 33, Folder 80)
    - Pollock, Griselda - "Artists Mythologies and Media Genius, Madness, and Art History", Undated; 193233 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Required and recommended reading lists, Undated; 193232 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Seminar in Femenist Theory Syllabus, Undated; 193231 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Spatiality and Women's Discourse syllabus, 1982; 193230 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Student Papers - "Margaret Fuller: A Rare Woman in Any Century", 1965; 193229 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - SUNY Albany, 2005; 193228 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Series XIV, Subseries B: Sociology Coursework, 193195
    - Collective Behavior - Notes and reading, 1985-1986; 193226 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Conteporary Sociological Theory - Final paper, 1981; 193225 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Conteporary Sociological Theory - syllabus, notes, readings, 1981; 193224 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - CUNY Graduate Center - Sociology Acceptance, letters of reference, 1981; 193223 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Development of Sociological Theories, 1981; 193222 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - "DisComforted Reading of Wharton's 'The Other Two'" - sociology: Prof. Caws, gender reading, 1986; 193221 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Final paper - Professor Oestereicher, 1982; 193220 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - History of American Sociology - Professor M. Brown, 1989; 193219 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Interdisciplinary Foundations of Sociology - Michael E. Brown; Notes, syllabus, article, 1988; 193218 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Linguistics - Notes and reading (1 of 2), 1987; 193217 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Linguistics - Notes and reading (2 of 2), 1987; 193216 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Max Weber's Sociology - notes, readings, bluebook, 1985-1986; 193215 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Production Notebook - unknown project, Undated; 193214 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Research for Caws Paper - sociology notes, Undated; 193213 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Sociology - articles for M. Brown's poststructuralism class and notes, 1990; 193212 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Sociology - Fetishism paper for Arowitz; Lawrence paper for Brown, 1989; 193211 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Sociology notes - notebook, Undated; 193210 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Sociology notes - notebook, Undated; 193209 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Sociology notes - notebook and inserts for Deviance Theory, Undated; 193208 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Sociology notes - notebook and inserts including Berkshire Conference on the history of women, Undated; 193207 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Sociology notes - Statistics notebook and inserts, Undated; 193206 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Sociology of Culture readings (1 of 3), 1984; 193205 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Sociology of Culture readings (2 of 3), 1984; 193204 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Sociology of Culture readings (3 of 3), 1984; 193203 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Sociology of Culture - Spring 1984 syllabus, notes, articles, 193202 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Sociology papers: ERA, Undated; 193201 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Sociology - photocopied articles, Undated; 193200 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Sociological Statistics - notes and homework, Undated; 193199 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Spring course offerings for Ph.D. program in Sociology at CUNY Grad. Center, 1982; 193198 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - The Structure of Social Theory - notes, Undated; 193197 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Term Papers from school, Undated; 193196 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Series XV: Printed Material, 193047
  Series XV: Printed Material includes books, pamphlets, magazines, etc. from Lynne Tillman's library. These materials contain pieces written by Lynne Tillman and/or friends of Tillman. Some books have inscriptions from the author.
  A list of titles that were separated from the collection, some of which were cataloged in Bobcat, is available here.
  - Acker, Kathy - "In Memoriam to Identity" New York, Grove Weidenfeld; uncorrected proof, 1990; 193193 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Aim for Life: The Congessions of a Hope Foemd typescript by Timothy Leary and Brian Barritt, Undated; 193192 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Alan S__ - Forlorn Matter; Sad Sad Hole, Undated; 193191 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Albery, Nicholas - "How to Save the Body", Undated; 193190 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Archipel Ago, 1999; 193189 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Arden, Jane - Vagina Rex and the Gas Oven typescript for Franklin Furnace Bookworks exhibit, Undated; 193188 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Arnold, William - "Shadowland" about Frances Farmer; Source material for "Committed", Undated; 193187 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Autre Monde, 1977; 193186 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Bartgerald, Jogn - "Applegather: A Mythical American Underground", etchings by Julie Maas with letter from J. Maas, 1978; 193185 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Bartlett, Neil - "The House on Brook Street" uncorrected proofs, 1996-1997; 193184 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Bartlett, Neil - "Ready to Catch Him Should He Fall" uncorrected proofs, 1991; 193183 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Beiles, Sinclair - "Delina" Rotterdam: Cold Turkey Press for Franklin Furnace Bookworks exhibit, Undated; 193182 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Beiled, Sinclair - "Sacred Fix" Rotterdam: Cold Turkey Press, for Franklin Furnace Bookworks exhibit, 1975; 193181 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Before Information #3/4, 1995; 193180 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Benet, Stephen Vincent - "America" New York: Overseas Editions for Franklin Furnace Bookworks exhibit, 1944; 193179 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Between Artists - Bound galley, Undated; 193178 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Blagg, Max and Gibson, Ralph - "Pink Instrument" uncorrected proof, Undated; 193177 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Blank Postcards, Undated; 193176 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Bowles, Paul - "Next to Nothing" Kathmandu: Sharada Printing Press, 1976; 193175 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Brakhage, Stan - "A Moving Picture Giving and Taking Book" West Newbury MA: Frontier Press, 1971; 193174 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Broadway Columbia Daily Spectator, 1986; 193173 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Brown, Michael E.; Martin, Randy; Rosengarten, Frank; Snedeker, George; eds. "New Studies in the Polotics and Culture of U.S. Communism", 1993; 193172 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Bryson, Scott - "The Chastised Stage" Saratoga: ANMA Libri & Co.; inscribed to Lynne Tillman by author, 1991; 193171 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Cheever, Susan - "Note Found in a Bottle" Inscribed to Lynne Tillman by author, 1999; 193170 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Coda: Poets and Writers Newsletter 8:5, 1981; 193169 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Cohen, Ira - "12 Photographs" Kathmandu: Cold Turkey Press, Undated; 193168 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Cohen, Ira - "From the Divan of Petna Vogt" for Franklin Furnace Bookworks exhibit, 1976; 193167 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Cohen, Ira - "Gilded Splinters" for Franklin Furnace Bookworks exhibit, 1977; 193166 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Cohen, Ira - "Poem for LaMalinche", Undated; 193165 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Cohen, Ira and Young, Dana - "Opium Elementals" for Franklin Furnace Bookworks exhibit, 1976; 193164 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Davidson, Robyn - "Ancestors: A Novel" New York: Simon & Schuster; inscribed to Lynne Tillman by Author, 1989; 193163 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - DeLynn, Jane - "Don Juan in the Village", 1990; 193162 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - diPrima, Diane - "Loba Part II", Pt Reyes and Kathmandu: Eidolon Editions, 1976; 193161 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Disend, Michael - "Stomping the Goyim" New York: Croton Press; inscribed to Lynne Tillman by author, 1969; 193160 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - "Don't Call Before Noon" - Jennifer Blowdryer, 1992; 193159 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Eagleton, Terry - "Marxism and Literary Criticism" annotated, 1976; 193158 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Earl Russell - "The Full and True Text of a Notorious, Remarkable and Visionary Speech made by Jogn, Viscount Amerley, Earl Russell, on the 18th, of July, 1978..., Undated; 193157 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Ehrlich, Willi - "Goethe's House on the Frauenplan at Weimar", 1985; 193156 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Enzig, Barbara - "Life Moves Outside" inscribed, 1987; 193155 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Exhibition Catalogue - "Constructions of Meaning", 1991; 193154 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - The Fanatic magazine, Undated; 193153 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Ford, Charles Henri - "7 Poems", 1974; 193152 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Ford, Charles Henri - "Water from a Bucket"; DAP Books on Art and Culture Catalogue, 2001; 193151 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Foreman, Amanda - "Georgiana, Duchess of Devonshire" uncorrected proof, 2000; 193150 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Frauen und Film #32 - including Claudia Lenssen interviewing Heinz Emigholz, 1982; 193149 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Front Pages recording November 22, 23, 24, 25, Undated; 193148 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Gerth and Mills, eds. - From Max Weber: Essays in Sociology" annotated, 1958; 193147 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Gottlieb, Eli - "The Boy Who Went Away" New York: St Martins Press; inscribed to Lynne Tillman by author, 1997; 193146 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Greenwald, Ted - "Licorice Chronicles" New York: The Kulchor Foundation; inscribed to Lynne Tillman by the author, 1979; 193145 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Greenwald, Ted - "Use No Hooks" New York: Asylum's Press; inscribed to Lynne Tillman by the author, 1980; 193144 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Guiles, Fred Lawrence - "Legend: The Life and Death of Marilyn Monroe" annotated, 1984; 193143 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Gwerder, Urban - "Tilt" inscribed, 1967; 193142 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Gysin, Brion, 1994; 193141 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Hadley, Leila - "A Journey with Elsa Cloud" New York: Books & Co./ Turtle Point; inscribed to Lynne Tillman by the author, 1997; 193140 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Hardwick, Elizabeth - "Seduction and Betrayal: Women and Literature" annotated, 1975; 193139 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Haring, Keith - "Keith Haring" Appearances Press, 1981; 193138 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Haynes, Jim - "More Romance, Less Romanticism" inscribed by author to Lynne Tillman, 1980; 193137 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Haynes, Jim - "Thanks for Coming!" inscribed by author to Lynne Tillman, 1986; 193136 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Haynes, Jim - "Workers of the World, Unite and Stop Working!" in Russian and French; inscribed by author to Lynne Tillman, 1978-1993; 193135 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Haynes, Jim and Jeanne Pasle-green - "Hello, I Love You!" Jean Lafitte Editions; inscribed to Lynne Tillman by Jim Haynes; Franklin Furnace Bookworks exhibit, 1974; 193134 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - het Ewicht #3, 1, 5, 6, 1977-1978; 193133 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Hill, Iris Tillman - "Migrant Summer", 1991; 193132 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Honig, Edwin - "Only the Living Know Brooklyn" manuscript, Undated; 193131 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Horn, Roni - "You are the Weather", 1997; 193130 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Indiana, Gary - "Resentment" bound galley, 1997; 193129 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - "Ins and Outs" vols. 1:1 (1978), 1:3 (1978), 4/5 (1980), 1978-1980; 193128 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - The Insect Trust Gazette #1 - inscribed to Lynne Tillman from Robert Basara, 1964; 193127 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Karbo, Karen - "The Diamond Lane" uncprrected proof, 1991; 193126 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Kasper, Michael - "All Cotton Briefs", "The Shapes and Spacing of the letters", "Billy! Turn Down that TV!", "Plans for the Night", Undated; 193125 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Kiernan, Frances - "Seeing Mary Plain: A Life of Mary McCarthy" New York: WW Norton & Co.; advance proof, 2000; 193124 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Konkret, 1982; 193123 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Kramer, Larry - "Reports from the Holocaust" New York: Penguin Books; inscribed to Lynne Tillman by Simon Watney, 1990; 193122 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Landes-Levi - "Poems" for Franklin Furnace Bookworks exhibit, 1977; 193121 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Lastname, Bradley - "Bile", Undated; 193120 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Leary, Joanna and Timothy - "Neurologic", 1973; 193119 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Levy, William, ed. - "Wet Dreams" for Franklin Furnace Bookworks exhibit, 1973; 193118 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Levy, William and Michell, John - "Souvenir Programme" Crambride: Cokaygne Press; Franklin Furnace Bookworks Exhibit, 1973; 193117 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Lummerding, Susanne - "Weibliche" Asthetik? Moglichkeiten und Grenzen einer subversion von codes, 1994; 193116 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - MacLise, Angus - "Checklist" compiled by Gerard Malanga, 1974; 193115 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - MacLow, Jackson - "French Sonnets" Milwaukee: Membrane Press; inscribed to Lynne Tillman by the author, 1989; 193114 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Mailer, Norman - "Marilyn: a Biography" annotated, 1973; 193113 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Map: Milan, Undated; 193112 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Map: U.S., Undated; 193111 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Messer, Ellen and May, Kathryn E. - "Back Rooms: Voices from the Illegal Abortion Era" uncorrected proof, 1988; 193110 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - McNulty, Faith - "Must they Die?" New York: Doubleday & Co.; inscribed to Lynne Tillman by the author, 1971; 193109 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - McNulty, Faith - "The Wildlife Stories" Garden City: Doubleday; inscribed to Lynne Tillman by the author, 1980; 193108 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Michael, Magali Cornier - "Feminism and the Postmodern Impulse" Albany: SUNY Press; inscribed to Lynne Tillman by the author, 1996; 193107 (Box 38, Folder 18)